Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Hauptmann, Gerhart. (I) (Box 3252)
- Hausding (Box 3253)
- Hausmann, R. (Box 3254)
- Hauy (Box 3255)
- Haven, S. (Box 3256)
- Havlick (Box 3257)
- Haweis (Box 3258)
- Hawkesworth (Box 3259)
- Hawksby (Box 3260)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1804-1864 (Individual works) D (continued) (Box 3261)
- Hay, D. (Box 3262)
- Hayakawa (Box 3263)
- Hayastani (Box 3264)
- Haydn, Joseph (Box 3265)
- Hayes, John (Box 3266)
- Hayley (Box 3267)
- Hays, I. (Box 3268)
- Haywood (Box 3269)
- Hazart, Cornelius (Box 3270)
- Hazlitt, William, 1811-1893 (Box 3271)
- Headlam (Box 3272)
- Health and food (Box 3273)
- Healy, W. (Box 3274)
- Hearnshaw (Box 3275)
- Heat (surname) (Box 3276)
- Heaton, G. (Box 3277)
- Heber (Box 3278)
- Hebrew with Kishon (Box 3279)
- Hecker, M. (Box 3280)
- Hedge, T. (Box 3281)
- Heer (Box 3282)
- Hefner, R. (Box 3283)
- Hegel, G.W.F. (continued) (Box 3284)
- Hegel and the Modern State (Box 3285)
- Hei lung (Box 3286)
- Heidegger, Martin, 1889 (continued) (Box 3287)
- Heidelberger (Box 3288)
- Heidmann, J. (Box 3289)
- Heilhbronn (Box 3290)
- Heim, Norman (Box 3291)
- Heindl (Box 3292)
- Heine, Heinrich-Addresses, essays, lectures (Box 3293)
- Heinen (Box 3294)
- Heinrich, R. (Box 3295)
- Heinz (Box 3296)
- Heiss (Box 3297)
- Hekking (Box 3298)
- Hele (Box 3299)
- Helie (Box 3300)
- Hellenike (Box 3301)
- Hellers (Box 3302)
- Hellwig (Box 3303)
- Helmore, G. (Box 3304)
- Helsinki (Olympic Games) (Box 3305)
- Hembyze, Jan (Box 3306)
- Hemingway, Wilfrid (Box 3307)
- Hemptinne, J. (Box 3308)
- Henderson, Emily (Box 3309)
- Henderson, S. (Box 3310)
- Hendro (Box 3311)
- Henke, Karl (Box 3312)
- Hennecke, Frank (Box 3313)
- Henninger (Box 3314)
- Henrico (Box 3315)
- Henry IV (Box 3316)
- Henry, D. (Box 3317)
- Henry, W. (Box 3318)
- Henry James' criticism (Box 3319)
- Henslow, John (Box 3320)
- Hentz (Box 3321)
- Her, Ge (Box 3322)
- Herbal Medications (Box 3323)
- Herbert, H. (Box 3324)
- Herbich, John (Box 3325)
- Herder (Box 3326)
- Heredia (Box 3327)
- Hergberg, Max (Box 3328)
- Heritage of Copernicus (Box 3329)
- Herman, Frank (Box 3330)
- Hermann, Paul (Box 3331)
- Hermeus, Ferdinand (Box 3332)
- Hernandez, Dilio (Box 3333)
- Hernandez Lopez, Carlos (Box 3334)
- Herodianus (Box 3335)
- Heroine of Rescue (Box 3336)
- Herrell, Wallace (Box 3337)
- Herrick (Box 3338)
- Herrliberger, David (Box 3339)
- Herron, Orley (Box 3340)
- Hershberger, H. (Box 3341)
- Herts (Box 3342)
- Herve (Box 3343)
- Herzberg (Box 3344)
- Herzog, H. (Box 3345)
- Hesing (Box 3346)
- Hess, J. (Box 3347)
- Hesse, Hermann (subject) (Box 3348)
- Hessiche Landeskirche (Box 3349)
- Hetten (Box 3350)
- Heuschen, Helmut (Box 3351)
- Hevrat ha-Ovdim (Box 3352)
- Hewlett, Maurice Henry (Box 3353)
- Heydon (Box 3354)
- Heymans (Box 3355)
- Heywood, Thomas, d. 1641 (author) (Box 3356)
- Hibbs, J.R. (Box 3357)
- Hickok (Box 3358)
- Hidalgo (Box 3359)
- Hidude Tenakh (Box 3360)
- Hieronymus (forename) (Box 3361)
- Higginbottom, S. (Box 3362)
- High (surname) (Box 3363)
- Higham (Box 3364)
- Hightower (Box 3365)
- Hijikata (Box 3366)
- Hilal (Box 3367)
- Hildebrand, R. (Box 3368)
- Hiles (Box 3369)
- Hill, C. (Box 3370)
- Hill, George Francis (Box 3371)
- Hill, M. (Box 3372)
- Hill, W. (Box 3373)
- Hiller (Box 3374)
- Hilliers (Box 3375)
- Hilprecht (Box 3376)
- Himerius (Box 3377)
- Hinchcliff (Box 3378)
- Hindermann (Box 3379)
- Hines family (Box 3380)
- Hinsch (Box 3381)
- Hintze, R. (Box 3382)
- Hippolytus (Box 3383)
- Hiraoko (Box 3384)
- Hirose (Box 3385)
- Hirsch, F. (Box 3386)
- Hirschfield, H. (Box 3387)
- Hirth (Box 3388)
- Hisely (Box 3389)
- Hispanicus (Box 3390)
- Histoire de l'U (Box 3391)
- Histoire des j. (Box 3392)
- Histoire h. (Box 3393)
- Historia co. (Box 3394)
- Historia de las l. (Box 3395)
- Historia ducum (Box 3396)
- Historia sacra (Box 3397)
- Historic (Box 3398)
- Historical and f. (Box 3399)
- Historical e. (Box 3400)
- Historical Records Survey. Alabama (Box 3401)
- Historical sketches (Box 3402)
- Historie z. (Box 3403)
- Historische Kommission fur N. (Box 3404)
- Historische und (Box 3405)
- Historiska (Box 3406)
- History of American s. (Box 3407)
- History of D. (Box 3408)
- History of J. (Box 3409)
- History of our (Box 3410)
- History of steam (Box 3411)
- History of the first (Box 3412)
- History of the rise (Box 3413)
- History of the W. (Box 3414)
- Hitchcock, F. (Box 3415)
- Hitler, Adolf (continued) (Box 3416)
- Hitopadesa (Box 3417)
- Hizb (Box 3418)
- Hluchaniuk (Box 3419)
- Ho, ch'u (Box 3420)
- Ho la memoria fatta (Box 3421)
- Ho-shen (Box 3422)
- Hoadly, Benjamin (author) (Box 3423)
- Hoare, J. (Box 3424)
- Hobbes, Thomas (continued) (Box 3425)
- Hobson (Box 3426)
- Hochman (Box 3427)
- Hockett (Box 3428)
- Hodge, J. (Box 3429)
- Hodgkins (Box 3430)
- Hodson (Box 3431)
- Hoeflich (Box 3432)
- Hoelderlin, Friedrich (continued) (Box 3433)
- Hoenich (Box 3434)
- Hoerter (Box 3435)
- Hoff (Box 3436)
- Hoffman, J. (Box 3437)
- Hoffmann, Ernest T. (continued) (Box 3438)
- Hoffmann, Karl (Box 3439)
- Hofheinz (Box 3440)
- Hofmann, U. (Box 3441)
- Hofstatter (Box 3442)
- Hogarth, William (continued) (Box 3443)
- Hogg, James, 1770-1835 (Box 3444)
- Hohenzollern, House of… (Box 3445)
- Hojoki (Box 3446)
- Holanda (Box 3447)
- Holbrook, Josiah (Box 3448)
- Holden, S. (Box 3449)
- Holfeld, Hermann (Box 3450)
- Holland, H. (Box 3451)
- Hollande (Box 3452)
- Holles (Box 3453)
- Hollister (Box 3454)
- Hollywood in… (Box 3455)
- Holme, C. Geoffrey (Box 3456)
- Holmes, John (Box 3457)
- Holmes, P. (Box 3458)
- Holovanivsskyi (Box 3459)
- Holt, Joseph (Box 3460)
- Holtze (Box 3461)
- Holy Roman Empire. Reichstag (Box 3462)
- Holzman (Box 3463)
- Hombrecillo (Box 3464)
- Home of Washington (Box 3465)
- Homer (Box 3466)
- Homer. Ilias et Odyssea (Box 3467)
- Homer (subject) (M) (Box 3468)
- Homero (Box 3469)
- Homme en d. (Box 3470)
- Homsey (Box 3471)
- Honduras, Secretaria (Box 3472)
- Honey (surname) (Box 3473)
- Hong Kong Gazetteer (Box 3474)
- Honolulu (author) (Box 3475)
- Hood, F. (Box 3476)
- Hook (Box 3477)
- Hooker, T. (Box 3478)
- Hoor, M. (Box 3479)
- Hoover Institution (Stanford University) (Box 3480)
- Hope, R. (Box 3481)
- Hopkins, E. (Box 3482)
- Hopkins, Prynce (Box 3483)
- Hopper (Box 3484)
- Horace (Horatius Flaccus) (Dacier) (Box 3485)
- Horace (Horatius Flaccus) (Epodi) (Box 3486)
- Horan (Box 3487)
- Hori, Motoko (Box 3488)
- Horkheimer, Max (Box 3489)
- Horn, W. (Box 3490)
- Horne family (Box 3491)
- Horovitz (Box 3492)
- Horse (Box 3493)
- Hort (Box 3494)
- Horvat, Branko (Box 3495)
- Hosegood, Lewis (Box 3496)
- Hosmer (Box 3497)
- Host (Box 3498)
- Hotelling (Box 3499)
- Hou, K'ang (Box 3500)
- Hough, Leon F. (Box 3501)
- Houot, Georges (Box 3502)
- House of Hapsburg (Box 3503)
- Housing Betterment (Box 3504)
- Houston, P. (Box 3505)
- Hovell (Box 3506)
- How he did it (Box 3507)
- How to know the aquatic plants (Box 3508)
- Howard, E. (Box 3509)
- Howard, N. (Box 3510)
- Howarth (Box 3511)
- Howe, L. (Box 3512)
- Howell, John (Box 3513)
- Howell's School (Box 3514)
- Hows (Box 3515)
- Hoyt, E. (Box 3516)
- Hrdlicka, Ales (author) (Box 3517)
- Hrvatski (Box 3518)
- Hsi hsiang chi (Box 3519)
- Hsi-ti (Box 3520)
- Hsia, David (Box 3521)
- Hsiang-hsia (Box 3522)
- Hsiang pa (Box 3523)
- Hsiao, E. (Box 3524)
- Hsiao-ming (Box 3525)
- Hsiao yao yu (Box 3526)
- Hsieh L. (Box 3527)
- Hsien chieh tuan (Box 3528)
- Hsien tai fu (Box 3529)
- Hsin, Chi-chung (Box 3530)
- Hsin Chung-kuo ti I (Box 3531)
- Hsin k'an ts'an ts'ai (Box 3532)
- Hsin shih san shih nien (Box 3533)
- Hsing (Box 3534)
- Hsing shih su sung fa lun (Box 3535)
- Hsu (author and title entries interfiled) (Box 3536)
- Hsu-chou shih (China) (Box 3537)
- Hsu, Hsueh-erh, comp. (Box 3538)
- Hsu, Nai (Box 3539)
- Hsu, So-fang (Box 3540)
- Hsu, Wen-t'ing (Box 3541)
- Hsueh (author and title entries interfiled) (Box 3542)
- Hsueh i. (Box 3543)
- Hsuen hsi liao fa (Box 3544)
- Hu, Chu (Box 3545)
- Hu, L. (Box 3546)
- Hu, S. (author and title cards interfiled) (Box 3547)
- Hu, Y.S. (Box 3548)
- Hua-hsia chih sheng (Box 3549)
- Hua shang t'o chih (Box 3550)
- Huan (author and title entries interfiled) (Box 3551)
- Huang, Chieh (Box 3552)
- Huang-ho san chi (Box 3553)
- Huang, Kuei (Box 3554)
- Huang, S. (Box 3555)
- Huang, Tsu-ying (Box 3556)
- Huard (Box 3557)
- Hubbard, H. (Box 3558)
- Huber, F. (Box 3559)
- Hubler (Box 3560)
- Huden (Box 3561)
- Hudson, R. (Box 3562)
- Hudson's Bay Company (subject) (M) (Box 3563)
- Hueck (Box 3564)
- Huerlimann (Box 3565)
- Huff, Ann M. (Box 3566)
- Hughes (Box 3567)
- Hughes, J. (Box 3568)
- Hughes, R. (Box 3569)
- Hugo (forename) (Box 3570)
- Hugo, Victor Marie, 1802-1845 (Individual works) Travailleurs de la mer (Box 3571)
- Hugues (surname) (Box 3572)
- Hui und Pfu der Welt (Box 3573)
- Hukum p. (Box 3574)
- Hull, W. (Box 3575)
- Hulten, O (Box 3576)
- Human g. (Box 3577)
- Human rights b. (Box 3578)
- Humanismo (Box 3579)
- Humbert, H. (Box 3580)
- Humboldt, Wilholm (subject) (Box 3581)
- Hume, David, 1711-1776 (subject) (H) (Box 3582)
- Hummel (Box 3583)
- Humphrey, W. (Box 3584)
- Hunayn, Riyad (Box 3585)
- Hung ch'I ko (Box 3586)
- Hung lou meng Hsi yu chi (Box 3587)
- Hung yen hsin yu (Box 3588)
- Hungary. Orszaggyules (Box 3589)
- Hunt, Chester L. (Box 3590)
- Hunt, Mabel (Box 3591)
- Hunter, B. (Box 3592)
- Hunter, S.C. (Box 3593)
- Huntington (surname) (Box 3594)
- Huntley (Box 3595)
- Hupp (Box 3596)
- Hurlbutt (Box 3597)
- Hurtado (Box 3598)
- Husain, S. (Box 3599)
- Huse (Box 3600)
- Husserl, Edmund (continued) (Box 3601)
- Hut (Box 3602)
- Hutchinson, D. (Box 3603)
- Hutchison, Keith (Box 3604)
- Hutterian (Box 3605)
- Huxley, Aldous Leonard (Box 3606)
- Huxley (titles, etc.) (Box 3607)
- Hvidt, K. (Box 3608)
- Hyde, G. (Box 3609)
- Hydrology year book (Box 3610)
- Hymnal (Box 3611)
- Hyperion (Box 3612)
- I.A.V. (Box 3613)
- I call… (Box 3614)
- I ching yun ta i (Box 3615)
- IEEE Control (Box 3616)
- I found A. (Box 3617)
- IITT (Box 3618)
- I.M. (Box 3619)
- I pa i she (China) (Box 3620)
- I shih ti ai (Box 3621)
- IUCN (continued) (Box 3622)
- IA (Box 3623)
- IAkushkin family (Box 3624)
- IAroshevskii, A.V. (Box 3625)
- Ibach (Box 3626)
- Ibero-Romance (Box 3627)
- Ibn al-Maqaffa (Box 3628)
- Ibn Gabbi (Box 3629)
- Ibn Masarra (Box 3630)
- Ibn Tulun, A. (Box 3631)
- Ibsen (Box 3632)
- Icaza, Jorge (Box 3633)
- Ichim, F. (Box 3634)
- Idaho (State) (author) (Box 3635)
- Idea of peace… (Box 3636)
- Idees recues (Box 3637)
- Ideologie (Box 3638)
- Idris, Y. (Box 3639)
- If you look… (Box 3640)
- Iglesia (Box 3641)
- Ignatius, of Loyola, Saint (continued) (Box 3642)
- Ihde (Box 3643)
- I'jaz al-Qur'an (Box 3644)
- Ikeda, Yasaburo (Box 3645)
- Ikonomika (Box 3646)
- Iles (Box 3647)
- Ill (Box 3648)
- Illinois. Department of agriculture (Box 3649)
- Illinois. Secretary of state (Box 3650)
- Illinois short fiction (Box 3651)
- Illustrated comic alphabet (Box 3652)
- Illustrators of Alice… (Box 3653)
- Ilyin, A.V. (Box 3654)
- Image (Box 3655)
- Images on water (Box 3656)
- Imana Castro, T. (Box 3657)
- Imhoff (Box 3658)
- Immersion (Box 3659)
- Immunology letters (Box 3660)
- Impartial i. (Box 3661)
- Imperial review (Box 3662)
- Importance (Box 3663)
- Improved Housing (Box 3664)
- In Asien waehst der (Box 3665)
- In love and trouble (Box 3666)
- In re Molineux (Box 3667)
- In the heat (Box 3668)
- In w. (Box 3669)
- Inba al-ghumr (Box 3670)
- Income… (Box 3671)
- Incwadi (Box 3672)
- Independent Order of Odd Fellows. New Haven (Box 3673)
- Index of art… (Box 3674)
- Index to the P. (Box 3675)
- India (S) (Box 3676)
- India. Department of… (Box 3677)
- India. Forest department (Box 3678)
- India. Ministry of Law (Box 3679)
- India. Planning Commission (continued) (Box 3680)
- India League (Box 3681)
- Indian Council for R. (Box 3682)
- Indian journal of d. (Box 3683)
- Indian politics (Box 3684)
- Indiana (Territory) (Box 3685)
- Indiana. State Defense Council (Box 3686)
- Indiana University (Publications) (S) (Box 3687)
- Indianapolis Museum of Art-P (Box 3688)
- Indice gramatical… (Box 3689)
- Individual and the o. (Box 3690)
- Indogermanische D. (Box 3691)
- Indonesia. Badan Penyelenggara (Box 3692)
- Indonesia. Departemen Anggaran… (Box 3693)
- Indonesia. Departemen Perburuhan (Box 3694)
- Indonesia. Direktorat Djenderal Kehutanan L. (Box 3695)
- Indonesia. Direktorat Jenderal Pertanian (Box 3696)
- Indonesia. Kantor W. (Box 3697)
- Indonesia. Perpustakaan Negara (Box 3698)
- Indonesian labor force (Box 3699)
- Industrial America (Box 3700)
- Industrial location (Box 3701)
- Industrial survey (Box 3702)
- Industrieller Friede (Box 3703)
- Infantry officer (Box 3704)
- Influence of the G. (Box 3705)
- Information radio (Box 3706)
- Informe que… (Box 3707)
- Ingemisco (Box 3708)
- Ingle, D. (Box 3709)
- Ingraham, Joseph Holt (continued) (Box 3710)
- Inhoffen, H. (Box 3711)
- Inman (Box 3712)
- Innis, H. (Box 3713)
- Inochi to katachi (Box 3714)
- Inoue, Tetsujiro (Box 3715)
- Inquiry into the social… (Box 3716)
- Insdorf, C. (Box 3717)
- Inskeep, G. (Box 3718)
- Institut arkheologii (continued) (Box 3719)
- Institut de la vie (Box 3720)
- Institut ekonomiki (continued) (Box 3721)
- Institut francais d'Athenes (Box 3722)
- Institut fur Europaische Geschichte (continued) (Box 3723)
- Institut fur Zeitgeschichte (Box 3724)
- Institut Ilmiah Angkatan Laut (Box 3725)
- Institut istorii (Box 3726)
- Institut Laus-Langevin (Box 3727)
- Institut miroval literatury (continued) (Box 3728)
- Institut national des arts (Box 3729)
- Institut Russkogo (continued) (Box 3730)
- Institut voennoi istorii (Box 3731)
- Institut za nacionala istorija (Box 3732)
- Institute for Latin American Integration (Box 3733)
- Institute for U. (Box 3734)
- Institute of Economic Growth (Box 3735)
- Institute of International Education (Box 3736)
- Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 3737)
- Institute of race relations (Box 3738)
- Institute of mental health… (Box 3739)
- Institutionen fur Maskinelement (Box 3740)
- Instituto Central de F. (Box 3741)
- Instituto de Estudos da Religiao (Box 3742)
- Instituto Geografico Militar (continued) (Box 3743)
- Instituto Nacional de Antropologia (continued) (Box 3744)
- Instituto Nacional de Estatistica (Box 3745)
- Instituto Superior… (Box 3746)
- Institutum Europeum (Box 3747)
- Instytut Badan Literackich (Box 3748)
- Instytut istorii partii (Box 3749)
- Insulaires (Box 3750)
- Integration question (Box 3751)
- Interaccion fuerzas… (Box 3752)
- Inter-American Development Bank (Box 3753)
- Inter-American U. (Box 3754)
- Interest of England (Box 3755)
- Intermarriage (Box 3756)
- International American Conference (Box 3757)
- International Association of Art Critics (Box 3758)
- International Astronomical Commission (continued) (Box 3759)
- International bibliography… (Box 3760)
- International Business Machines Company (continued) (Box 3761)
- International chemical (Box 3762)
- International commission on N. (Box 3763)
- International conference of (Box 3764)
- International conference on F. (Box 3765)
- International conference on Public Education (Box 3766)
- International Conference on Tools… (Box 3767)
- International Congress of botany (Box 3768)
- International Congress of philosophy (Box 3769)
- International Congress on Ecology (Box 3770)
- International Council of Religious Education (Box 3771)
- International Design Conference (Box 3772)
- International Education (Box 3773)
- International Federation of… (Box 3774)
- International Geographical Congress (continued) (Box 3775)
- International Homeric Symposium (Box 3776)
- International Institute of Documentation (Box 3777)
- International Journal of Mathematics (Box 3778)
- International Labor Office. C (Box 3779)
- International Labor Office. R (continued) (Box 3780)
- International Labor Organization (continued) (Box 3781)
- International macroeconomics (Box 3782)
- International Monetary Fund (continued) (Box 3783)
- International Organization for the… (Box 3784)
- International Power Company (Box 3785)
- International Rice Research Institute (continued) (Box 3786)
- International Series of monographs (continued) (Box 3787)
- International Sociology (Box 3788)
- International Symposium of F. (Box 3789)
- International Symposium on Genetics... (Box 3790)
- International Symposium on Seed... (Box 3791)
- International theory... (Box 3792)
- International Union of Biological Sciences (Box 3793)
- International Union of Pure and Applied Physics (Box 3794)
- International Workshop on L. (Box 3795)
- Internationale studier (Box 3796)
- Internationale Symposium zur... (Box 3797)
- Interprete (Box 3798)
- Inter-university Case Program (Box 3799)
- Inti Karka (Box 3800)
- Introduction (Box 3801)
- Introduction to logic (Box 3802)
- Introduction to the science. (Box 3803)
- Invasion within (Box 3804)
- Inventario dos (Box 3805)
- Investigacion u. (Box 3806)
- Investors chronicle (Box 3807)
- Ioannis T. (Box 3808)
- Iorga, Nicolae (author) (Box 3809)
- Iowa. Secretary of State (Box 3810)
- Ipousteguy, J. (Box 3811)
- Iran and Pakistan (Box 3812)
- Ireland. Parliament (author) (Box 3813)
- Ireland, W. (Box 3814)
- Iris Laboria (Box 3815)
- Irish delftware (Box 3816)
- Irkutsk (Box 3817)
- Irons (Box 3818)
- Irving, E. (Box 3819)
- Irving, Washington. Sketch Book (Box 3820)
- Iryo hosho (Box 3821)
- Isaacs (Box 3822)
- Isaiah Targum (Box 3823)
- Ise shu (Box 3824)
- Isherwood, Christopher (continued) (Box 3825)
- Ishii, R. (Box 3826)
- Ishin ni ikiru (Box 3827)
- Isin, R. (Box 3828)
- Islam and modernity (Box 3829)
- Islamic U. (Box 3830)
- Isma'il (Box 3831)
- Isolation of membranes... (Box 3832)
- Israel. Information Services (Box 3833)
- Israel after Begin (Box 3834)
- Israfel (Box 3835)
- Issues in the... (Box 3836)
- Istituto c. (Box 3837)
- Istituto Italiano (Box 3838)
- Istituto per la Storia (Box 3839)
- Istoricheskaia m. (Box 3840)
- Istoriia M. (Box 3841)
- Istoriia VKP (Box 3842)
- Isvara (Box 3843)
- Italia nostra (Box 3844)
- Italians in America (Box 3845)
- Italy. Comitato (Box 3846)
- Italy. Ministero dell'interno (Box 3847)
- Italy, Treaties (Box 3848)
- Itineraires a... (Box 3849)
- Ito, Selichi (Box 3850)
- Itsikel (Box 3851)
- IUdkevich (Box 3852)
- Iv, J. (Box 3853)
- Ivanov, N. (Box 3854)
- Ivanys, Vasyl' (Box 3855)
- Ivi (Box 3856)
- Iwaki (Box 3857)
- Iwasaki (Box 3858)
- Iz (Box 3859)
- Izac (Box 3860)
- Izibongo (Box 3861)
- Izumo (Box 3862)
- J.D. (Box 3863)
- Jaba (Box 3864)
- Jack (surname) (Box 3865)
- Jackson, Andrew, 1767-1845 (author) (Box 3866)
- Jackson, G. (Box 3867)
- Jackson, Joseph (Box 3868)
- Jackson, Thomas Graham (Box 3869)
- Jacob ben D. (Box 3870)
- Jacob, Raul (Box 3871)
- Jacobite (Box 3872)
- Jacobs, Rainer (Box 3873)
- Jacobson, Nathan (Box 3874)
- Jacomb (Box 3875)
- Jacquot (Box 3876)
- Jaeger, K. (Box 3877)
- Ja'fari (Box 3878)
- Jagger (Box 3879)
- Jahn, Otto (Box 3880)
- Jahrbuch fuer (Box 3881)
- Jaime (forename) (Box 3882)
- Jakarta, Indonesia. Lembaga (Box 3883)
- Jakosky (Box 3884)
- Jaloux (Box 3885)
- Jamar (Box 3886)
- James (surname) (Box 3887)
- James, H. (Box 3888)
- James, Henry, 1843-1916 (continued) (Box 3889)
- James, Thomas (Box 3890)
- James G. Birney and his time (Box 3891)
- Jamet (Box 3892)
- Jamin, A. (Box 3893)
- Jan Bloch (Box 3894)
- Janes (Box 3895)
- Jank, M. (Box 3896)
- Janowitz (Box 3897)
- Janssen, L. (Box 3898)
- Janvier (Box 3899)
- Japan. D. (Box 3900)
- Japan. Kaigun-History (continued) (Box 3901)
- Japan. Kokuseiin (Box 3902)
- Japan. Mombusho (continued) (Box 3903)
- Japan. Rikugun (continued) (Box 3904)
- Japan. Sorifu (continued) (Box 3905)
- Japan (titles, etc.) (Box 3906)
- Japan trade review... (Box 3907)
- Japanese property (Box 3908)
- Jaquet (Box 3909)
- Jargon (Box 3910)
- Jarry, B. (Box 3911)
- Jaspers, Karl (author) (Box 3912)
- Jatar (Box 3913)
- Javet (Box 3914)
- Jay, John, 1817-1894 (Box 3915)
- Je (Box 3916)
- Jean Gabin (Box 3917)
- Jeannet (Box 3918)
- Jednak (Box 3919)
- Jefferson, Thomas (author) (Commonplace book) (Box 3920)
- Jefferys, C.W. (Box 3921)
- Jehser (Box 3922)
- Jellinger (Box 3923)
- Jen kuei yu (Box 3924)
- Jen min yin yueh (Box 3925)
- Jenaische (Box 3926)
- Jenkins, John (Box 3927)
- Jenkys (Box 3928)
- Jennings, S. (Box 3929)
- Jensen, J. (Box 3930)
- Jeppe (Box 3931)
- Jerome, Saint (Hieronymus) (author) (Box 3932)
- Jersey (surname) (Box 3933)
- Jervell (Box 3934)
- Jessen, K. (Box 3935)
- Jesuits. Letters from missions (North America) (Box 3936)
- Jesus Christ-Biography (Box 3937)
- Jesus Christ-Drama (Box 3938)
- Jesus Christ-Messiahship (Box 3939)
- Jesus Christ-Person and offices (continued) (Box 3940)
- Jesus Christ in Literature (Box 3941)
- Jeux de sang... (Box 3942)
- Jewish Agency for Israel (continued) (Box 3943)
- Jewish Theological Seminary of America (Box 3944)
- Jews. Liturgy and ritual (H) (Box 3945)
- Jews advocate (Box 3946)
- Ji, Myon-kwan (Box 3947)
- Jih-pen kuan kan (Box 3948)
- Jillson, Willard R. (Box 3949)
- Jimenez de Asua (Box 3950)
- Jinji Gyossi (Box 3951)
- Jisa, Jan (Box 3952)
- Jo, Hector Ayon (Box 3953)
- Joan of Arc, Saint (Trial) (Box 3954)
- Job (Box 3955)
- Jockers, Ernst (Box 3956)
- Joenniemi, Pertti (Box 3957)
- Joh. Enschede (Box 3958)
- Johannes Isaaci, Hollandus (Box 3959)
- Johansson (Box 3960)
- John of Salisburg (Box 3961)
- John (surname) (Box 3962)
- John Carter Brown Library (continued) (Box 3963)
- John Henry (Box 3964)
- John O (Box 3965)
- Johns, F. (Box 3966)
- Johns Hopkins University. School of Engineering (Box 3967)
- Johnson, B. (Box 3968)
- Johnson, Donald (Box 3969)
- Johnson, Gertrude (Box 3970)
- Johnson, James Weldon (L) (Box 3971)
- Johnson, Lorenzo D. (Box 3972)
- Johnson, R. Brimley (Box 3973)
- Johnson, Samuel, 1696-1772 (Individual works) Diary (Box 3974)
- Johnson, Samuel, 1709-1784 (subject) (Box 3975)
- Johnson, Treat Baldwin (Box 3976)
- Johnson Society (Box 3977)
- Johnston, J. (Box 3978)
- Johnston, William (Box 3979)
- Joint (Box 3980)
- Joint Committee on Public Morals (Box 3981)
- Joinville (Box 3982)
- Jolly (Box 3983)
- Jonas (Box 3984)
- Jones, B. (Box 3985)
- Jones, Dennis (Box 3986)
- Jones, G. (Box 3987)
- Jones, Horatio (Box 3988)
- Jones, John Paul (Box 3989)
- Jones, Mary (Box 3990)
- Jones, Rufus Matthew (Box 3991)
- Jones, William (Box 3992)
- Jongh (Box 3993)
- Jonsson (Box 3994)
- Jordan, David Starr (Box 3995)
- Jordan, T. (Box 3996)
- Jorissen (Box 3997)
- Jose Marti (Box 3998)
- Joseph (surname) (Box 3999)
- Josephson (Box 4000)
- Josephus, Flavius (Box 4001)
- Joslin (Box 4002)
- Joubert (Box 4003)
- Jourdain, M. (Box 4004)
- Journal des Poetes (Box 4005)
- Journal of Applied Meteorology (Box 4006)
- Journal of Dairy Science (Box 4007)
- Journal of Indian Museums (Box 4008)
- Journal of Philology (Box 4009)
- Journal of the (Box 4010)
- Journalism (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 4011)
- Journeys (Box 4012)
- Jovial (Box 4013)
- Joyce, James, 1882-1941 (Individual works) Joy and Sorrow (Box 4014)
- Joyce, P. (Box 4015)
- Juan (forename) (Box 4016)
- Juana (Box 4017)
- Judah (Box 4018)
- Judd, S. (Box 4019)
- Judicial selection (Box 4020)
- Judisches Museum (Box 4021)
- Jugend einer... (Box 4022)
- Jui (Box 4023)
- Julian, Emperor of Rome, 331-363 (Box 4024)
- Jullian, R. (Box 4025)
- Jung, Carl Gustav, 1875- (continued) (Box 4026)
- Jung ai lu (Box 4027)
- Jungle jest (Box 4028)
- Junkers (Box 4029)
- Jurgons, R. (Box 4030)
- Jusserand (Box 4031)
- Justice first (Box 4032)
- Justus Perthes' Atlas Andiquus (Box 4033)
- Juvencus (Box 4034)
- K book (Box 4035)
- Ka (Box 4036)
- Kabisch (Box 4037)
- Kadari, M. (Box 4038)
- Kaehler (Box 4039)
- Kaestner, Erich (Box 4040)
- Kafka, G. (Box 4041)
- Kage to koe (Box 4042)
- Kahl, K. (Box 4043)
- Kahn, O. (Box 4044)
- Kaibel (Box 4045)
- Kaino, M. (Box 4046)
- Kaiser, G. (Box 4047)
- Kajima, Hisa (Box 4048)
- Kakuk, Z. (Box 4049)
- Kalckreuth, L. (Box 4050)
- Kalid, ben Jariki (Box 4051)